Guide to the Cornell Migrant Program records, [ca. 1953-2005]
Cornell Migrant Program records, [ca. 1953-2005]
- Series XL. Albany Day Marches/Press
  - Daily News - Farmwork Still a Thankless Job, 2000 (Box 34, Folder 68)
  - Daily News - Farm Work Still Gets a Raw Deal - Alcantara and Werner, 2001-02-25 (Box 34, Folder 69)
  - Daily News - Let Egan Take Up O'Connor' Quest, 2001 (Box 34, Folder 70)
  - Albany Day, 2001 (Box 34, Folder 71)
  - Albany day press, 2001 (Box 34, Folder 72)
  - Albany Day photos, 2001 (Box 34, Folder 73)
  - Daily News advocates rally to get farmworkers a day off, 2000 (Box 34, Folder 74)
  - Albany Day photos, 2002 (Box 34, Folder 75)
  - Albany Day press, 2002 (Box 34, Folder 76)
  - March to Albany photos, 2003 (Box 34, Folder 77)
  - March to Albany, 2003 (Box 34, Folder 78)
  - March to Albany press, 2003 (Box 34, Folder 79)
  - Press farmworkers rights, 2003 (Box 34, Folder 80)
  - March to Albany press, 2004 (Box 34, Folder 81)
  - March to Albany programs and events, 2004 (Box 34, Folder 82)
  - March to Albany publicity, 2004 (Box 34, Folder 83)
  - March to Albany, 2004 (Box 34, Folder 84)
  - March to Albany photos, 2004 (Box 34, Folder 85)
  - Press farmworkers rights, 2004 (Box 34, Folder 86)
  - Farmworkers march to Albany, 2005 (Box 34, Folder 87)
  - Farmworker voices workshop, 1998 (Box 34, Folder 88)
- Series XLI. Coursework
  - Farmworker course journals, 2007 (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Farmworker course journals, 2007 (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Farmworker course journals, 2007 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Farmworkers course, 2002-2004 (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - Farmworkers course - Kay Embrrey's service coordination file, 2004 (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - Farmworkers course reading, 2004 (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - Farmworkers course readings, 2004 (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - Farmworkers course readings - Clete Daniel, 2004 (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - Farmworkers course readings - Nelson Bills, 2004 (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - Farmworkers course - Literacy volunteers training, 2004 (Box 43, Folder 7)
  - Farmworkers course - Photographs, 2004 (Box 43, Folder 8)
  - Farmworkers course - papers, 2004 (Box 43, Folder 9)
  - Farmworkers course, 2005 (Box 43, Folder 10)
  - Farmworkers class papers, 2005 (Box 43, Folder 11)
  - Farmworkers class handouts, 2005 (Box 43, Folder 12)
  - Farmworkers class handouts, 2005 (Box 43, Folder 13)
  - Farmworkers class handouts, 2005 (Box 43, Folder 14)
  - Farmworkers course, 2007 (Box 43, Folder 15)
  - Farmworkers course - Engman materials, 2007 (Box 43, Folder 16)
  - Farmworkers course journals, 2007 (Box 43, Folder 17)